<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Joy of Coding</title>
    <link>https://pbhrdwj.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Joy of Coding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 13:14:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pbhrdwj.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ubiquitous Abomination</title>
      <link>https://pbhrdwj.github.io/post/safe_agile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 13:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbhrdwj.github.io/post/safe_agile/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2003, when I was a novice, entry-level, software engineer, one of my initial projects was in the Enterprise Application Integration (EAI) space. As it was my first job, I was all gung-ho about the thought of building something new and perhaps too eager to learn and apply whatever little programming skills I had acquired so far.
But all my hopes were dashed, when I realized soon enough, that for enterprise projects like this, there was a huge time lag between project kick-off and the first line of code being written.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obligatory Greeting</title>
      <link>https://pbhrdwj.github.io/post/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbhrdwj.github.io/post/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Even though its still early days of the Covid outbreak, this pandemic induced lockdown has already changed a lot of things for and around me.
So, despite a restless 6 year old at home and a whole lot of extra household chores to contend with, I suddenly find myself with a little bit of additional leisure time, never seen before. Hence, this is perhaps an opportune moment, to pause and reflect at things gone by, and look forward to, great things yet to come.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>